[music]
>> So, this trip was unexpected. One day,
not long ago, Laura proposed the idea of
me joining her on her birthday trip. And
you guys know, this is my eat, pray,
love year, as I've said multiple times,
which means less overthinking, more
yeses in general. So, aligning myself
with that thought process, I said yes.
And trust, there was a lot of
overthinking involved. I mean, for one,
Laura and I have never even met up in
person, and I'm sure you guys have seen
the story times of falling out when on a
trip with another girl. Nigeria of all
places is a bit random, also, especially
because I still have to go back to my
own country, hopefully soon. On top of
all of that, last minute I found out I
didn't have a vaccination needed to
enter the country. Despite all of the
anxieties and what-ifs, and even a
slight chance that I wouldn't even make
it in the country, I made my way over to
Lagos. 15 hours of travel time to see
and celebrate a girl I've never met
before. [music] Only God knew how this
was going to go at this point.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hey guys,
welcome to the vlog. That was such a
long travel situation, too. That was a
10-hour flight. It was from Toronto to
Washington, which is an hour-long
flight, and then Washington Washington
to Lagos, which is a 10-hour flight. And
I was knocked out on that flight. Like,
I That literally felt like a 2-hour
flight. I was asleep the whole time
because I didn't really sleep that well
the night before. Anyways, I'm here in
Lagos. I'm at the Delborough Hotel
currently.
I'm here like this is super last minute.
I'm even surprised that I'm even here.
It's Lara's birthday and I decided to
come along basically for the ride on a
whim. I'm here for 10 days you guys.
We'll see how this goes. I don't know.
This is my first time in Nigeria. I am
excited. I feel like I'm going to have a
good time. I don't know.
>> [laughter]
>> So basically I didn't know that Lara
booked she got like the mini suite. I
got like the basic room. This is not the
basic room but it's a level up from the
basic room. But I'm like why didn't you
tell me that she got the suite cuz maybe
I would have gotten the suite or maybe
not. I don't know. But yeah, this is the
room. It's not bad but then it's also
like pretty small in here I feel like.
Anyways, I'm about to go figure out
what's going on. What are we doing
tonight cuz we are going out tonight. So
hot it's so humid. My curls fell within
like a second of stepping out into this
heat.
But it's nice and AC in here and I'm
freaking starving. So I'm going to see
maybe I can go get some food.
Um the food on this flight was like the
worst food I've had on a business flight
ever. Like that was so bad. That was so
[music] bad.
>> [music]
>> This is what I'm wearing. Don't mind
this big ass bag. I just brought my
laptop because we're going to get our
makeup done. I decided to say yes to get
my makeup done even though I feel a
little
unsure about it. Like I don't know. I
feel weird about people doing my makeup.
But anyways, I ended up saying yes. I
didn't want to stay alone here while
they went. So I low key had FOMO.
>> [music]
[singing]
>> I'm a fighter [music] I forget.
Hey.
>> [music]
[music]
>> All right, you guys. I'm back in the
room. My makeup is done and this is what
it looks like. I need like a good light
source to show you guys. I do feel like
it's a bit dramatic. I'm going to like
fix it up a bit and like soften it
because yeah, it's like too dramatic for
me. It's more than I'm used to.
Everyone's like, "No, it looks good. It
looks good." And I was like,
I don't know. I just feel like the
makeup just feels too dramatic for me.
Like this is just not what I'm used to,
you know? But anyways, I'm going to
do my hair first because I'm just going
to straighten it and curl it and then
I'm going to fix up my makeup.
And then we're headed to
Panther. Mr. Panther. That's the first
stop for the night. So,
yeah. Lara's birthday is on Monday, I
think, by the way.
Cuz today is the 1st. Yeah, her her
birthday is on Monday. So, it's not her
birthday yet, but obviously we're going
to be celebrating
the whole time. So, [music]
>> [music]
>> I hope you guys can see me properly, but
this is what I'm wearing tonight. First
night out in Lakers. It's the House of
CB bandage dress. We're actually all
doing bandage dresses. So, we're all
going to be Barbie bandage dress vibes.
I'm doing my Renees, which I like
literally I don't I never wear these
heels, but I just wanted like heels that
matched my bag. And this is what I came
up with. Honestly, I don't know if I'm
like a fan of these heels. I just feel
like they're not they don't make my legs
look the best. I might change the heels,
to be honest with you guys, now that I'm
looking at myself. And then on top of
that, I dropped a little bit of like
body oil right here. Laura said to clean
it with micellar micellar water,
whatever it is. So, I'm hoping it dries
down like
good, but I don't know.
I fixed up my makeup a little bit. I
feel a lot more comfortable with how it
looks now. Uh, I'm getting tired.
Anyways, first night out in Lagos. I'm
really excited.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Guys, we are
No.
She's not desperate in your vlog. I'm
not putting that in mine. We are
at
What Where is this again? Oh, Panther
and now we're going to Marcopolo.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hey you guys. So, it's actually the next
day. I forgot my camera in the car
yesterday, so
I didn't vlog at all today. It's the
next night. It's currently 10:00 p.m.
But also, I did nothing today. I did
absolutely nothing. Um, I was in bed all
day. We ended the night
pretty early in the morning and then we
literally went straight to breakfast cuz
breakfast was already available
um, when we got back. I think it was
like 7:00 or 6:00 a.m.
So, I feel like I definitely experienced
Lagos like going out yesterday.
Like it was definitely buzz club, not a
club.
Buzz club, not a club. Also, a lot of
the places did not allow me to bring my
camera in.
So, yeah. After experiencing that,
I feel like I'm my energy is spent.
Like, oh my god. But, um
anyways, we're doing the movies today.
That's Lara, and these are the girls.
We're watching The Devil Wears Prada.
Oh, this is so cute.
>> You need three eyes.
>> I'll be your hostess this evening.
So, do you know where the ladies
restroom is? If you need anything, I'll
be outside.
>> [music]
[music]
>> 1 2 3
>> [music]
[music]
>> Put your ass up. 4
>> Yeah? Yeah? I've no idea. I'm expressing
>> [music]
>> After getting ready in Lara's room, I
went to change into this really cute
Meshki dress. You guys saw me talking
about this in the previous vlog. I
obviously did not vlog when I stepped
out, but lucky for you guys, I was
taking videos. So, you guys already know
the vibes.
>> [laughter]
>> Buzz club, not a club, not a club. By
the time we got out of the last spot, it
was daytime outside, and we were
starving. So, we stopped at Norma for a
bite, and then I knocked out in my bed.
We're headed to Slow today.
Quick, casual.
This is my outfit. We got ready so fast
today cuz like
time is running out. I just told Lara
like let's not do makeup cuz makeup is
It's going to take too long. Let's just
go, and then
when we come back, we can do our makeup
and stuff.
So.
We keep matching besties, you know.
You look so cutie.
Birthday girl. Okay.
We just came from Slow.
How was the food?
You didn't like it?
>> No.
>> I actually really liked the food at
Slow. I think it was really good and I
loved the vibes there. Like it was just
it was really nice. It was like a day
vibe. We haven't done like day vibes
yet. So, that was nice. It was a good
time. It's Laura's birthday I'm in So,
we're going to try and like make the
most of today and stuff and tomorrow.
So. Hey you guys. Okay, so I finally
like have a moment to just like chill
and talk to you guys, but I'm doing my
makeup. We're heading out again tonight.
It's Laura's birthday at midnight. So,
we're going on a boat first and then I
don't know. We'll see how the night
goes. But yeah, tomorrow's her birthday.
So, everything has been leading up to
this. Let's just finish doing my makeup
so we can head out of here. I feel like
you know when you're just doing your
makeup continuously on holiday, it just
gets so tiring. Like I'm already at that
point and it's what like day three. I'm
actually really enjoying Lagos. Like I'm
having such a good time here. I was
definitely nervous to come all the way
here to be honest cuz I'm like, "Damn, I
don't even know how this is going to
go."
But I feel like everything is like
working itself out like to be honest.
I'm having a good time. I'm enjoying. I
just want us to do more daytime things
cuz we've definitely been going out a
lot. Like I I want us to do like more
like brunch, like spa, things like that.
But I think after her birthday we'll
like do more of those sorts of things. I
even wanted us to take a Pilates class.
So, we'll see. Just doing my lip and
then I'm going to get dressed, and then
I'm going to head over to Laura's room.
I'm excited for tonight. I feel like
we're going to have a good night
tonight, so. The only thing is I need to
come back home early today because I
like I have a video due tomorrow. Oh my
god, guys. I hate the fact that I
actually have like work to do while I'm
on vacation, but it's just like tying up
loose strings, things that were due that
need to be refilled. So, I need to come
home early. I'm not going to be out
until 4:00 or 6:00 7:00 a.m. tonight.
I'm coming home. I told myself I want to
be back home by like 2:00 a.m.
All right, you guys. This is what I'm
doing for outfit. This set is Kookoo.
I'm wearing my slides, but I have my
heels in the bag because we're doing a
boat. I'm just going to start off with
slides, and then
we can change afterwards. Let's go see
what Laura is doing cuz we need to be
out of here. The driver is downstairs.
Let's see.
You ready?
>> Mhm.
>> I got a plane.
>> [music]
>> You just met
You're so famous.
>> Hi Bretman.
I ran into Bretman.
IT'S SO ILLEGAL. OH MY GOD, it's so
crazy.
>> Wait, what's your name?
>> Moneysada.
>> Moneysada?
>> Yeah.
>> Cool. Okay.
>> [laughter]
[music]
[singing]
>> Melenames.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hi.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Rise and shine,
you guys.
I'm so happy I actually remember to turn
the camera on this morning, but um I
just woke up. I realize like I take a
really long to wake up. Like I need like
an hour to like be okay, but I am now
awake.
I'm about to go get ready. I ordered a
coffee, and I actually have a video to
film today. Like
a makeup video. It needs to be submitted
today. I'm doing it pretty last minute,
but I've been procrastinating this video
for so long because it's basically me
refilming a video that they asked. I
don't think they're going to be
necessarily fully happy with the video
cuz I'm not in my usual setup, and I
don't know what the video's going to
look like cuz I'm not in my usual setup,
and I'm just like I don't want to do
this. Regardless of that, it's not that
big of a deal. I'm going to get myself
together, do my hair, set up my phone,
and get to working. And then once that's
off of my chest, I think I'm going to
feel a lot better cuz I've like been
like a bit nervous about that. Anyways,
we were supposed to do boat day
yesterday. It started raining as soon as
we got ready, so hoping to do that for
today. I'm supposed to get my hair
redone at some point, maybe today. I
feel like this whole Nigeria trip has
been a ton of like we just don't have
time. Like we'll plan to do this, this,
and that, and then the day comes, and we
just have no time, you know?
Or we'll get like one of the three
things done in the day. Like I think a
lot of things that we plan to do is just
like unrealistic and just never ends up
happening.
>> [laughter]
>> Which I'm not mad at. Like this trip
isn't like a super strict itinerary for
me. It's kind of like a go with the flow
trip, which I'm enjoying the going with
the flow. The only thing is moving
forward, bus, club, another club,
another club, another club. I want to
relax on that vibe. I want to do I I
think I said this before, but I
definitely like especially because today
is a Monday, the weekend is over. We
need to like focus on like daytime
things.
We Me and Laura keep saying this and
then we always fall into the trap. And
then you know why it's a trap? Because
when you go out, you don't get back
until late. So then you sleep really
late in the next day and it just takes
your whole day essentially, which is
just not ideal. So then you're only you
only get ready again at night. So it's
like a cycle almost that you fall into.
It's a trap.
We're not falling for it today. Cuz
yesterday I said I was wanted to be home
by 2:00 a.m. I didn't I didn't I don't
think I slept until 4:00 a.m. so. I got
them to bring me the Americano the
almond milk. Brought me ice. So let's do
a little mixology situation.
[\h__\h]
All right, you guys. We just
All I did was like beast dance RDLs and
then I did
biceps curls into shoulder press some
some some some.
I did work myself up into a little bit
of a sweat, but
I just want to feel active. Like I'm not
even trying to
do anything for real. I do feel a little
bit nauseous though. I don't think I've
been eating enough. Anyways,
we're going to go get some breakfast
and
edit after.
Hey, you guys. Okay.
I got myself ready. This is the outfit.
This one is too cute. All All the tags
are on.
But I don't have scissors, so I'm going
to go downstairs and get them to cut the
tags. But I'm wearing a bikini because
we're going to
I think we're going to like a beach
house restaurant vibe. My new shoes.
This is the back.
>> [music]
[music]
[singing]
>> The flashes are playing up.
>> [music]
[music]
>> This is Aqualina.
He's giving us a tour of like the
property. I feel like we can get some
banging pictures here.
The freaking boat just messed up my
hair.
But hopefully I can
salvage it somehow.
Thank you.
It's like an apartment, I guess.
Okay, let's go. Order up.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Lara, don't kill her.
>> [laughter]
>> What's the tea? This is a good week for
me to decide not to vlog. I'M LIKE
>> [screaming]
>> HEY YOU GUYS. I FEEL LIKE MY CAMERA
MIGHT FOG UP.
>> YEAH.
>> It's fogging up.
Let me wipe you.
We came back from the beach house, I
took a shower, took my makeup off, and
we're now about to head into the car.
I'm just waiting for Laura to get
downstairs. We're going to get a bite to
eat, but like something super chill. As
you guys can see, I have no makeup on
and I'm wearing a very casual outfit.
And I brought my laptop because I have
something to edit. I'm just waiting.
There's something last minute that I
need to do. That's the vibes for
tonight. Super chill. I told you guys
we're not doing bus, club, another club
for a minute, okay? I mean, it's
literally Tuesday, so there's not much
going on. But, yeah, it's chill vibes
and then hopefully, you know, we can get
an early night in tonight. There she is.
Oh, no way.
Oh, I love this. So pretty.
Thank you.
Finally, some Nigerian food. Like, oh my
god, we've been eating like
The party of the chicken is good.
This is gizzard.
Gizzard.
Oh, gizzard. Didn't you just say
gizzard?
Looks like beef.
>> [music]
>> Thank you.
>> No, you need to get a coffee machine.
>> [music]
>> Hey you guys, my hair is done again. I'm
looking good. Back to factory reset. Cuz
you guys know I wet my hair and I made
it like super puffy. So, I'm just hoping
that as soon as I step outside it
doesn't like puff up again cuz this
looks really good.
We just like straightened, redid the
front, washed it, redid it, and then
straightened it and curled it.
Okay you guys, hair is done. The
humidity is not letting me breathe as
you guys can see. We curled my hair and
everything just for it to look like
this. Whatever, it's cool.
I already set myself up. I already set
the expectation that this might happen,
so it's it's cool. We're at back at
Slow. I'm going to grab a quick bite and
then we're going to start shopping. I
want to go to some of the Nigerian
brands like Kartoumba. I just hope I
have enough time because it's currently
4:00 p.m. A lot of things close at 6:00.
I'm going to grab a quick bite
then head out. There's also a store like
in the same compound as Slow that I want
to go to.
Um
yeah. I was supposed to meet up with
Lara, but I'm probably going to meet up
with her in bit later.
So,
that's the plan.
Thank you so much. Have a good night.
Now we go to
Temple Muse for shopping.
This is the first top that I found. This
is from the brand I Am Me Sigo. I Am Me
Sigo.
It's so cute, but this is their small. I
asked [music] if they had a smaller size
and they don't, but this, if it fit
perfectly,
would eat. Second dress. So, this is a
medium. Again, it's the only one they
have. Ideally, I would get a small of
this. It's [music] like too big for me.
And so, um, the lady was like, "You can
get a tailor to
make the belt smaller." But it basically
just goes up like this. What designer is
this? This is Tangerine Tiger. This is a
large dress that I wanted to try on. I
kind of just wanted to try her on just
to see. She looked really nice and
dramatic, but she doesn't fit and it's
the only one they have. So, the brand is
I Am Me Sigo, I want to assume is how
you say it, but I don't think I'm
getting anything from this store, so we
are headed to the next one. Temple Muse
was nice and cute. It seemed like almost
like a concept store. They had a lot of
like Nigerian designers, but they didn't
have lots of sizes or anything. So, the
items that I that I liked, the only size
they had was the one that was
um,
displayed. So,
yeah. But anyways,
next stop.
Okay, guys, Rendoll was actually
successful. I bought something, the pink
dress that you you saw me trying on.
It's just that they had it a size too
big. I actually ended up sizing down two
sizes and I purchased it. They're going
to deliver it on Saturday cuz they
actually need to make it. I'm happy I
got something here. So, we're heading
back out tonight. I'm wearing this dress
from Kookai. We're doing dinner.
I'm a bit late. I'm about to head out. I
didn't even finish tying up my heels.
This dress is kind of cute now that I'm
looking at it in the
Like I was like, this is basic. I don't
really want to take pictures, but
I don't know. Maybe iPhone pictures.
We'll see.
Ooh.
I feel like I would should have worn
this dress to the club that night.
Anyways, all right, it's time to go.
Oh, it's foggy.
Thank you.
Happy birthday.
>> [laughter]
>> Stop.
Okay, wait. Let me get this on video as
well.
>> You look like I can't sing.
>> Whether I can sing or not, you're going
to hear my voice.
>> Alexis, you're really scary.
>> Guys, I thought
they had breakfast food here, but I
think they stopped serving breakfast.
So, we're considering going somewhere
else.
>> But that place is 25 minutes away.
>> Finally, we made it.
Before I even fainted in Nigeria, I
don't even know if they're how they're
going to bring me home because I
I'm I was so hungry, I wouldn't have
woken up for a good couple of days.
Maple.
Thank you. Hello.
>> That's what you ordered?
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> Okay, I'll just get your um full
American [music] breakfast.
>> Full American breakfast?
>> Yeah, with um
with the sausage.
>> Chicken sausage, how do you want them?
>> Uh scrambled.
>> [music]
>> Thank you.
Breakfast is served.
Thank you.
Hertumba
Yeah. All right, guys.
We're going to Hertumba now. We're going
to see what we can find in here.
You miss it.
I tried this top on. I got it in a
small. It snatches you so well. Like
I'm like super snatched. I can barely
breathe, but I kind of like it. I don't
know.
I don't know.
I'm trying on this pink one as well.
But they only have it in medium.
Yeah, it's too big.
>> Where would you wear this to?
>> I don't know, like an event.
>> [laughter]
>> It's giving big hips. Oh my gosh.
I already have a big butt.
I don't mind a little extra that.
Okay. I think the top is cute with like
a basic like bottoms. Like white. The
top is actually cute. Does it fit?
Or no?
It fits? Does it fit though?
>> Yeah, you just try it on.
>> Okay, let me let me let me take my dress
off and so I can try it properly.
>> It's actually cute.
thinking so.
>> look extra AF.
>> Yeah, like I don't know where I would
wear this.
>> Yeah, the color is nice on you.
>> But I think just the top.
>> With that white trousers.
>> Aw,
damn.
Hello you guys.
>> [clears throat]
>> I took a little bit of a nap.
Honestly,
that was not a good nap. I'm just bad at
napping. I'm going to Lara's room. I'm
about to do my makeup.
We're so extra, okay? I don't even know
why we have someone doing our makeup.
She just
was saying, "Should we do our makeup?"
And I was like,
"Sure." Just cuz I'm tired and we're
kind of both tired and it's always
easier to have somebody do it for you
versus doing it for yourself. Even
though they do do my makeup a little bit
more dramatic than I do it, I don't like
it fully, but it's easily fixable. I
feel like everything in like hair in
Nigeria is just so convenient. So, you
can just easily get someone to do your
makeup, come to your hotel room.
And even though it's like we're not even
doing anything. Like it's literally not
even that deep.
But,
we just be doing [\h__\h] honestly.
So, yeah.
Hello.
>> Oh my god, guys. I don't even know if I
told you guys my camera broke yesterday.
It's like done. I just dropped it when I
was taking pictures.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Okay, turn to this side.
Back to your camera.
You can come in.
>> That was a physical.
>> Okay, that's what she said to my camera.
>> I'm downstairs and got dressed. This is
what we put on. This is a
Kukoo set. Once again, she's so cute. I
hope I'm not doing too much though, cuz
we are going out and the skirt is
definitely a little
you know.
But
I love this dress. I hope I get a
picture.
Anyways.
>> [snorts]
>> We're late as [\h__\h]
Cute.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Good morning, you guys. So, it is the
next day.
Today's Friday and I am finally getting
my hair done. I'm getting braids done,
which I'm so excited about. That's the
whole thing. When you go to Africa, you
have to get
some good teeny tiny braids. So,
I'm very excited. Like, I'm so excited.
I'm on the way now to my appointment.
And
I just hope that it doesn't take me all
day. We're kind of starting late cuz
it's almost already 2:00 p.m. It's 1:35.
So, ideally, I would have started this
early in the morning, but
so, I'm going to be there for a minute.
I'm not going to lie. My time in Nigeria
is slowly coming to an end cuz I'm
leaving on Sunday.
I'm leaving Sunday night though, like my
flight is at 11:00 p.m. So, I mean I
have some time to do some things during
the day, but like Saturday
is my farewell last day, which is
tomorrow.
So,
it's coming to an end. I have to say
though this trip was long, like I'm
actually excited to go home. It's kind
of dragging at this point. I'm happy I'm
getting my braids done today. I'm really
excited and to take this out. This
ponytail is so freaking tight, but
yesterday was a good time as well. You
know, same Lagos stuff, which is just
like going out and then going to go spot
to spot to spot to spot, which was fun
when we just got here, but it definitely
gets very repetitive very quickly.
Didn't sleep
last night.
I was feeling it.
Yeah, boy.
I don't know what I'm doing better.
It's good.
This is so relaxing.
Okay, you guys. I'm back from
getting my hair done. I was there for a
minute. I think I ended at like right
before 9:00, so like 8:40 was when we
were fully done and I was ready to step
out. But basically I just asked them for
like knotless. I didn't want it to be
too heavy or anything. I wanted very
natural and that's what I got. So, I'm
actually very happy. I'm thinking should
I have left out more baby hairs?
But, I don't think so.
Woo!
I Whenever I get braids done, I have
like such a like shiver-y feeling. Okay,
anyways.
Anyways, that's done. Which I'm really
happy about cuz finally my braids are
in. I don't have to think about my hair
for a minute. I'm going to be working
out when I get back. I don't have to
think about my hair. We're going out
tonight. By the way, this set from Zara.
So cute. So, so, so cute. Anyways, you
guys are also got food. We ordered food
from Noho. I've got my Imata ordered
delivered today. I'm going to like open
this and show you guys another time.
It's currently 9:00. I'm going to start
getting ready. I'm going to hop in the
shower. Start doing my makeup.
We're going out again.
Okay.
I'm not exactly sure what the specifics
are, but most likely we're going to end
up at the club again. I don't know.
Don't judge me. It's kind of just like I
feel like this is just what there is to
do here is like that's just what there
is to do is just to go out. So, I barely
have any outfits left, but I think I
have one more like nice going outfit.
And after that, it's wraps.
>> [laughter]
>> So, this night I wore this dress. Can
you guys believe this dress is Zara? I
actually got this in Madrid. Do you guys
remember? I literally showed it to you
guys when I was trying it on and I was
like, "I don't think it's cute, but it's
so fire. It's so tea." Anyways, went
out. Same old, same old, and then came
home.
Oh my god.
Oh my too.
Guys, she [music] wants me to try it on
my love.
That's how you say it, right?
>> Yeah, amala.
>> So, let's see.
Okay.
>> [music]
>> You like it?
Yeah.
>> [music]
[laughter]
>> Yum.
Big fish. Bye you guys. So, I'm back in
the room. Yeah, today we went to knock.
Today is my full my last full day in
Nigeria. Thoughts on Lagos, Nigeria? It
just feels like a simulation here. I
don't know. My experience isn't going to
be somebody else's experience, but it
literally feels like I'm in an alternate
universe. I don't know if that's a good
or bad thing, but that's just how it
feels. So, I feel like, okay, I'm
excited to just go back to reality cuz
I've been living
a life that is like not mine. Like it's
not me.
If that makes sense. And I have a lot of
things waiting for me. I have so much
work to do. I haven't posted a vlog. I I
I checked the YouTube Studio app and I
saw there was 27 days ago.
And I was like,
[\h__\h] that's so bad. I don't I don't
want to think about it. It's giving me a
lot of anxiety. Anyways, I'm just going
to start getting ready. Last night out
in Niger.
>> [laughter]
>> I need to be back We need to be back at
a reasonable time so I could still be
able to enjoy my day tomorrow because I
be out all night. However, I'm going to
try to make the most of tonight, okay?
It's my last night here.
>> [laughter]
>> I feel like those two me saying those
two things are clashing. I want to get
back at a reasonable time. I want to
make the most of my night. Ah,
I don't know which one is going to win.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Okay, the girls are ready to go out last
night. It's crazy because I literally
said this is my last night. I need to
make sure I make the most of it. Like
I'm trying to go all out. It's my last
night. I don't know what it is, but as
soon as I got to the spot, I was just
like not feeling it. I was like I think
I'm going to go back. And within an hour
of leaving, I was back in my hotel room,
makeup off, in my PJs, tucked in, and I
have photo proof.
Hello you guys. So, this is the state of
my room. I'm currently packing. It's the
next day, obviously. I'm about to head
out and go get some food. Let me just
head out.
We're going to stop by Laura's room
first.
She has a client today, so she's not
coming with me.
I'm wearing an Alo set. You guys, I
brought both of I brought Laura and I
tennis sets. This was actually supposed
to be her set because we were supposed
to go like doing paddle or something
like that. We did none of that [\h__\h]
Like we literally did nothing cute. We
were supposed to have a spa day.
All right you guys, so I'm headed to
Maple to get breakfast. Breakfast at
3:00 p.m. is kind of crazy, but
>> [laughter]
>> we've been having late breakfast every
day. I'm actually picking up Amy after
Maple. I'm just going to go home, finish
packing, go to the hotel, finish
packing, and
maybe we'll head back out
for a last
vibe before home time cuz my flight is
at 11:00 p.m. tonight. Yesterday we went
out and honestly I was only outside for
like 2 minutes. I feel like
I'm getting tired of like the constant
going out. I've been telling you guys
that I'm tired of it, but yesterday I
was like, "Yeah, let me just
go home." So, I actually left early.
We're supposed to go to multiple spots,
but I left after the first spot. Anyway,
I'm just going to make the most of Lagos
for the next couple of hours that I'm
here, and then it's home time.
>> It's going to be a week or 2 week long.
>> love me some week long.
>> Let's do YouTube it.
>> Mhm.
I'm all packed up. You guys are headed
to M.A.C.O.
for one last M.A.C.O. run.
>> [laughter]
>> And then it's home time.
Cheers.
What do you rate
this trip in Nigeria?
>> 10 out of 10.
>> 8 out of 10.
8 out of 10. [laughter]
>> Why? What do you rate it?
What would you rate it?
>> I would say a 7. I feel like we have But
the So, we were just saying that
basically like this trip was 10 days,
but it feels like we've been here for so
long. We had stuff happen literally like
every single day. Like
it feels like we've had a million lives
here. Like it's actually insane. I would
say a 7 out of 10.
>> What was it that made it
>> I think it's just all the anxiety that I
had. That's what made it bad.
>> Is it giving Duct Tape December with Amy
or what?
>> I'm just saying.
>> I want to ask Amy too cuz it's almost
like you were on this trip with us.
What would you
>> with you every single day.
>> Yeah. What would you rate What would you
rate your staycation?
Your Nigerian staycation.
>> 10 out of 10.
>> Really?
>> Yeah.
I had so much fun.
>> We're leaving soon. I have to leave here
at like 8:30. It's 7:10, so we actually
have time. I'm happy we came to Meko cuz
Meko is like my favorite spot. It just
feels like we're in Tulum over here.
It's such a vibe. It's so warm. There's
like a breeze going. From Meko, I went
straight to the airport and it was home
time. I had a great time in Nigeria. I
was there for 10 days, which is crazy.
Literally felt like I was just in
another world. But, fortunately or
unfortunately, it was back to reality
for me. But, I may be back at some
point. I don't know.